[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "American politician John McCain was incarcerated at the infamous Hoa Loa Prison, ironically called Hanoi Hilton.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters portrayed by actor Alec Baldwin was not a real life person?", "correct_answer": "Jack Ryan (The Hunt for Red October)", "incorrect_answers": ["Jimmy Swaggart (Great Balls of Fire!)", "James Doolittle (Pearl Harbor)", "Juan Trippe (The Aviator)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the five major crime families of New York in The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "Corleone, Tattaglia, Barzini, Stracci, Cuneo", "incorrect_answers": ["Bonnano, Cuneo, Stracci, Tattaglia, Gambino", "Tattaglia, Genovese, Barzini, Lucchese, Bonnano", "Genovese, Gambino, Colombo, Corleone, Massino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mahjong, a kong is a set of how many identical tiles?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "6", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Pretty in Pink, the character played by Molly Ringwald has a guest, named Long Duk Dong, who is a  foreign exchange student.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what geographic area is the koala endemic?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Tasmania", "Australia and Tasmania", "Australia and New Guinea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What musician is often referred to as The Man in Black?", "correct_answer": "Johnny Cash", "incorrect_answers": ["Seal", "Will Smith", "Prince"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of John Dillingers girlfriend in the 2009 movie Public Enemies?", "correct_answer": "Billie", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby", "Bonnie", "Becky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are two naturally round lakes in the world. One is near Zurich, Switzerland. The other is in this U.S. state.", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Minnesota", "Wisconsin", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does McClane, the protagonist of Die Hard, kill the terrorist, named Karl?", "correct_answer": "He doesnt", "incorrect_answers": ["Hangs him", "Shoots him", "Pushes him off the building"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these medical terms means difficulty in swallowing.", "correct_answer": "dysphagia", "incorrect_answers": ["dyspepsia", "dysuria", "dyspnea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US President to address the nation on TV?", "correct_answer": "Truman", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoover", "Eisenhower", "FDR"]}]